Wow this show is an awesome new episode
of batman beyond isn't it random black
man it isn't fair you bet it is hey look
look at that right on back man someone's
knock on your door come here God you
won't believe this cbpo what are you
doing here guys turn on the nose quickly
why Batman Batman Batman is on the nose
he's being charged for murder apparently
he's going crazy no yes bill he rapes
you man's ass no I know super beat his
ass wow I'm coming for ya huh what's
that sound oh oh no it's bad man it's
the doc now he's come to take me or no
c-3po what's going on what did you tell
ya oh he did nothing Ian tell us
anything Batman really does that sum if
if I find out you're lying I'll shove my
sis self of your ass you won't be able
you four eggs no calm down black
man Batman it's okay he didn't tell us
anything that's good that's very good
goodbye everybody you're lying I will be
back bar well well black man we better
not tell the two three yeah oh no out of
my way he's got a sword ah another
another now no no daddy's gonna stick a
sort of yes seichas big on boy oh my God
no stop it Batman yeah no I'm sorry you
had to see that Sonic dilemma tater sure
what she's Batman that's not really me
that many people are happiness can
people that's the jerk who disguises me
know yes he did you get over there he's
telling the truth haha Sonic oh oh my
God yes he is Wow
big on pride
you